caravanmagazine.in 2011-03-21

# The Caravan | Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
This policy covers how delhipress.in treats personal information that delhipress.in collects and receives. delhipress.in is protecting the privacy of internet users. This statement discloses the privacy practices for delhipress.in.

**Information we collect**  
Delhipress.in collects personal information when you register with delhipress.in. When you use delhipress.in’s products or services or when you visit delhipress.in pages or otherwise, the information may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, phone number, birth date, gender, zip /pin code, etc., and other such information about you which is not otherwise publicly available. Besides, delhipress.in automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, the page you request, etc. which you can edit your Account Information on delhipress.in at any time.

**Types of Data Collected and Tracked**  
The information Collected by Delhi Press Patra Prakashan Private Limited can be categories into two main segments: -  
1\. Information voluntarily provided by visitors and viewers to our website through registration that are mandatory.  
2\. Tracking Information gathered as visitors navigate through our site.

**Use of information collected**  
[Delhipress.in](http://www.delhipress.in/) uses the above information for the following general purposes: -  
a) To customize the content you see on the site or through personal emails, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, or send emails containing advertisements and newsletters suo-motu.

**Sharing of information**  
delhipress.in does not provide any personal information to any advertiser when you view a targeted advertisement either on the site or in your email inbox. Delhipress.in does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you to any third parties, except when specifically informed to you at the time of collection of the information and / or to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: -

  * We respond to court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of delhipress.in terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We may transfer information with our group companies. In this event, delhipress.in will not notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online, in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above.

**Change in Policy**  
By using the site, your consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the site by delhipress.in. Delhipress.in may update this policy from time to time. We may notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your delhipress.in account or by placing a notice on our site. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our site at least 7 days in advance of implementation. 

**Your Consent**  
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the delhipress.in services such as service announcements, administrative messages and the delhipress.in newsletter. We have physical and electronic safeguards to protect personal information about you and your delhipress.in account. Information is password-protected. By using our web site, your consent to collect, use, and disclosure of information by delhipress.in and to the terms of this privacy policy.

**Security**  
When you place an order on line, your personal information and credit card information will be secured before being sent over the Internet, making it virtually impossible for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred to delhipress.in. Your credit card information is always stored in encrypted form in a database that is away from our web site database so it is not connected to the Internet, and is therefore safe from hackers. **Kindly keep a copy of your proof of identity, address and credit card at the time of delivery for verification**.

**Disclaimer**  
To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures. For example, our servers are accessible only to authorized personnel and that your information is shared with respective personnel. Although we will try to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

**We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to refer to us at e-mail at[ _pawan.gupta@delhipress.in_](mailto:pawan.gupta@delhipress.in).**

**Shipping Policy**  
Following is our shipping policy. Kindly read it carefully and in case you have any queries, send e-mail to for further clarification.

  * A shipping charge is applicable on all items at delhipress.in. There is no minimum order value at delhipress.in across any of our categories.
  * At our store, you can order any product where the shipping period is between 7 to 12 days for India and one month for abroad. These orders cannot be cancelled since they are specifically packed and dispatched.
  * Shipment of items against an order is subject to availability and delivery is at the sole discretion of delhipress.in.
  * The shipping address is where you wish to receive your order. It could be your home or office or any other valid address. You must submit your shipping address correctly to ensure the delivery reaches you promptly.
  * Once you have placed an order, we will store your shipping address so that you don’t have to enter the address again. This is the Preferred Shipping Address.
  * Once any order and its payment are fully processed, we pack product(s) for shipping. This is done with special care, so that they reach you in perfect condition. Our courier delivers these items at the shipping address submitted by you while filling up the online order form.
  * Shipping time is the time taken to deliver an order at a shipping address, after the order has been shipped out. It depends on where the customer stays and on the shipping mode selected by you while filling up the online order form.
  * You may be subject to duties and taxes on certain items, which are levied once a shipment reaches your city/state/country. Additional charges for customs clearance must be borne by you. We have no control over these charges and cannot predict what they may be. Customs policies or entry tax vary widely from country to country and place to place. Additionally, when ordering from delhipress.in, you are considered the importer on record and must comply with all laws and regulations of the country in which you are receiving the goods.
